http://kopworld.net/privacy-policy/

your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Two Potential Summer Targets For Klopp
Just How Important Are These Two Players?
How does the current Liverpool lineup compare to the greatest teams…
Who Should Partner Virgil van Dijk Next Season?
This title challenge was different to the others
Videos
Features
World Cup quiz – Who made the cut?
Liverpool’s free transfer signings
Classic Liverpool wins at Old Trafford
What Happened to Liverpool’s Brightest Spanish Youngsters from the 2000s?
Privacy Policy
At Kopworld, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Kopworld and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, Kopworld makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Kopworld does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Kopworld send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
Kopworld has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Kopworld’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
If you require more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to use our contact form.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read More
